journalbuddies.com 2019-04-04

# Journal Buddies | Privacy Policy ⋆ JournalBuddies.com

## Journal Buddies AKA Blue Sky at Night Publishing — Privacy Policy

Blue Sky at Night Publishing has drafted this document, which details how we gather and disseminate information, in an effort to demonstrate our strong commitment to online privacy.

Please [contact us](https://www.journalbuddies.com/contact-us/) if you have any questions about our privacy policy.

 **Advertising Privacy Statement**

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behavior on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third-party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

 **For European Economic Area Residents**

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact AdThrive at [info @ adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.)

Use of Internet Protocol Address

We use your Internet protocol (IP) address for several reasons: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad demographic information.

Use of Registration Information

Our site’s registration area requires customers to supply contact information, such as name and e-mail address, and demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, or income level. We use this information to send you promotional materials from our company and from some of our partners. However, users may opt out of ? or opt in to ? these promotional e-mail messages at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.)

Use of Demographic Information

We also collect demographic and profile data that we use to tailor your experience at journalbuddies.com. Based on this information, we display products and content we feel you might interest you.

Use of Order Information

When you place an order, Blue Sky at Night Publishing requests information such as contact information, credit card number and demographic information. The contact information you provide is used to send you orders, company information and promotional material from our partners. You can opt out or opt in at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.)

Your financial information is used for the sole purpose of billing you for products and services. You Social Security number is used to identify you, and demographic data is collected to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel would interest you most.

Use of Online Survey Information

To participate in our online surveys, you will be required to supply contact and demographic information. [Company Name] uses this data to send you information about the company. We might use this information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt into our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site and used to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel would most interest you.

Use of Information Collected in Contests

To participate in our contests, you will be required to supply contact and demographic information. [Company Name] uses this data to send you information about the company. We might use this information to contact you as necessary. However, you may opt out of or opt into our mailings at any time. (See Opt Out/Opt In, below.) Demographic and profile data are collected at our site and used to personalize future visits by displaying the content we feel you would most interest you.

Public Forums Guidelines

Blue Sky at Night Publishing may offer chat rooms and bulletin boards. Please note that information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public. Use caution in disclosing any personal information.

Security

Blue Sky at Night Publishing features security measures to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information placed under our control.

Children’s Guidelines

We do not collect or use any online contact information or identifiable off-line contact information about a child without parental consent. We do not distribute personally identifiable information about children without parental consent. We do not give children the ability to post or distribute personal information without prior consent. We do not entice children with games or contests that would encourage them to disclose personal information.

Opt Out/Opt In

Blue Sky at Night Publishing allows users to opt out of receiving e-mail from us or our partners. To opt out of our mailing list you can send e-mail to a remove mailing list.

Correct/Update Personal Information

Blue Sky at Night Publishing allows you to change or modify your personal information by sending e-mail to a remove e-mail address or by visiting a designated customer service page.

Disclaimer

This site contains links to other sites. Blue Sky at Night Publishing is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites.

Contact Us

If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please [contact us:](https://www.journalbuddies.com/contact-us/)

Jill Schoenberg  
Blue Sky at Night Publishing  
Little Falls, MN 56345
